scientific.net 2019-12-16

# Imprint and Privacy Policy

### Trans Tech Publications Ltd:

Commercial Register No:

CH-020.3.006.960-0 

Company ID No:

CHE-107.913.675 

Telephone: 

+41 44 922 10 22

Address:

Kapellweg 8, CH-8806 Baech, Switzerland 

Director:

Anne-Kristin Wohlbier

VAT Tax Number:

CHE-107.913.675 MWST 

Bank contact:

Credit-Suisse AG   
PO Box   
8070 Zurich   
Switzerland   
Swift-Code/BIC-Nummer: CRESCHZZ80A 

IBAN / USD:

CH86 0483 5033 9209 9200 0 

IBAN / EUR:

CH59 0483 5033 9209 9200 1 

IBAN / CHF:

CH23 0483 5033 9209 9100 0 

### Trademark

Scientific.Net is a registered trademark of Trans Tech Publications Ltd. (hereafter “Publisher”). All rights reserved. 

### Privacy Policy

Publisher is committed to protect the privacy of your personal information as we understand and respect the rights of users for its protection and the importance of accurate and security-conscious use thereof. 

Appropriate administrative and technical data protection measures are implemented to protect the users against unauthorized access, misuse, loss, theft or disclosure of personal data. Regardless of type of personal information collected and processed by Publisher, all information is processed, retained and secured under the current Swiss legislation. We have drawn up this Privacy Policy to clearly describe how we treat the personal information you leave and entrust us when using www.scientific.net

### Collected Personal Information

Publisher offers various services for users worldwide. If you wish to use all or any of services we will ask you to provide information about yourself which the system indicates for carrying out the successful registration and opening the account for further use. 

**1\. Personal data:**   
To provide adequate services and to cover users’ wishes and requirements Publisher collects, processes, retains and uses your **personal data** : 

  * Personal names
  * Usernames and passwords
  * Contact details: phone number, e-mail address 
  * Affiliation/organization details
  * Professional background, preferences and interests
  * Payment information (based on different types of cooperation: subscription-based model, purchasing a product, open-access publication model)
  * Any content submitted by users
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**2\. User-related information:**   
Our site doesn’t require any personal information to enter if your intention is to visit it and make search through the available content for acquiring information of your current interest or request. The system may automatically collect electronic user-related information such as: 

  * Cookies
  * The source redirecting you to our website
  * Internet Protocol address and language used
  * Your country 
  * Date and time of your visit or request
  * Your device type and its requirements/solutions
  * Information on the operating system of your device

All these user-related data are collected by our server and kept strictly anonymous straight after its getting.

### Use of Personal Information

Publisher uses, processes the collected personal information exclusively for performing its obligations and providing offered services properly and timely to meet your needs and requirements. 

**Personal data** entered by you while registering the account to get benefits from our services or to subscribe to our newsletters are processed for the purpose of: 

  * Completing the registration, including acknowledgement of e-mail address and further informing you about its success
  * Identifying you when signing-in
  * Maintaining and administering the registered account
  * Keeping you informed about state of things in regard to the service you have chosen
  * Providing a customer care support 
  * Enlightening the up-to-date changes, possibilities, opportunities

**User-related information** automatically collected by our server is used for: 

  * Improving the technical solutions to the best possible level to respond your requests and needs
  * Adopting our site to the settings of your devices
  * Analyzing and optimizing the website
  * Ensuring the website security
  * Making a statistical analysis about the use of site
  * Gathering a geographic information exclusively for internal use
  * Detecting and fixing technical problems/bugs that may lead to difficulties in informational use of website, satisfying requests and providing all or any of services

### External Links

Publisher uses external links exceptionally for your convenience and benefits and with informative purposes, for instance, when you look through the detailed information about conferences or would like to share your article in social media. We strongly recommend you to acquaint with their private policies in order to avoid misunderstandings with supervening innocent infringement or misconduct. 

### Managing your personal information

Publisher highly respects the rights for protection of personal information and by no manner of means our Privacy Policy restricts your entitlements. Alongside with our control and security, you are free to manage your personal information at your discretion. 

  * You may change your personal information in the registered account or send the request to our support team.
  * You may deactivate your account, which may be restored if you change your previous decision.
  * You may revoke your consent about storage and sharing your personal data with Publisher at any time.
  * You may stop getting any our newsletters by unsubscribing from this service through the link available in each such letter.

We guarantee that Publisher is not using and will not use your personal data for trades with the third parties without your consent for this or in cases when it is required by the law.

### Changes and updates

Publisher reserves the right to update the text of this Privacy Policy without a prior notification of users. We recommend you to visit this page from time to time to be aware of all and any of state-of-the-art changes, amendments and additions to this statement. 

This Privacy Policy is based on Publisher’s Policy and Ethics, [Federal Act on Data Protection (FADP)](https://www.admin.ch/opc/de/classified-compilation/19920153/index.html) of 19 June 1992 (Status as of 1 January 2014) and accompanying [Swiss Federal Ordinance to the Federal Act on Data Protection](https://www.admin.ch/opc/en/classified-compilation/19930159/index.html) of 14 June 1993 (DPO) (Status as at 16 October 2012) and the [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679](https://gdpr-info.eu/)

All and any questions, complaints, requests and suggestions concerning Privacy policy should be directed to  [ info@scientific.net ](mailto:info@scientific.net)
